<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH labels</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table></csh_table>
		<fileId>EXT:ab_booking/locallang_csh.xml</fileId>
		<labelContext type="array">
		</labelContext>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="pluginSelection.description">Define the view</label>
			<label index="pluginSelection.details"><![CDATA[ On this TAB you enter
						<ul>
							<li><b>Calendar</b>: Show Calendar for one ore more Product IDs</li>
							<li><b>Availability Form</b>: Show Form to Check the Availability</li>
							<li><b>Booking Form</b>: Form for entering the user data and to do the booking.</li>
						</ul>
						 ]]>
			</label>

			<label index="ProductID.description">Select the products you want to be used in this widget.</label>
			<label index="ProductID.details"><![CDATA[
			In the right box, you find all available products.

			If the box is empty, you first have to enter the storage pid where your products,
			prices and seasons are stored.
					]]>
			</label>

			<label index="numCheckNextMonths.description">Define how many months in the future the plugin accepts bookings.</label>

			<label index="enableCalendarBookingLink.description">Enable booking links on available dates in the calendar.</label>
			<label index="showDateNavigator.description">Show date navigation above the calendar.</label>
			<label index="numCheckDaySteps.description">Set the day steps in the availability-check form. E.g. To allow only week bookings, set this value AND numCheckMinInterval to 7.</label>
			<label index="numCheckMaxPersons.description">Shows only up to this maximum in selector box. Even if the capacity over all is higher. Leave empty for autoselect the maximum capacity!</label>
			<label index="EmailAddress.description">Overwrite the Email-Address of the Sender: This will overwrite system wide configuration. To avoid bad spam-headers, it's recommended to use proper SMTP configuration of your TYPO3 installation. In this case keep this entry empty!</label>
			<label index="EmailRealname.description">Overwrite the Name of the Sender: This will overwrite system wide configuration. To avoid bad spam-headers, it's recommended to use proper SMTP configuration of your TYPO3 installation. In this case keep this entry empty!</label>
		</languageKey>

		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="pluginSelection.description">Define the view</label>
			<label index="pluginSelection.details"><![CDATA[ On this TAB you enter
						<ul>
							<li><b>Kalender</b>: Show Calendar for one ore more Product IDs</li>
							<li><b>Verfügbarkeitsprüfung</b>: Show Form to Check the Availability</li>
							<li><b>Buchungsformular</b>: Form for entering the user data and to do the booking.</li>
						</ul>
						 ]]></label>

			<label index="ProductID.description">Wählen Sie die Produkte, die Sie in diesem Plugin berücksichten wollen.</label>
			<label index="ProductID.details"><![CDATA[ Wenn Sie keine Produkte sehen, müssen Sie zunächst die Page-ID des Sysfolders
				(unten). Alternativ können Sie den "General Record Storage Place" für diese und alle untergeordneten Seiten in den
				Seiteneinstellungen setzen.
					]]></label>

			<label index="enableCalendarBookingLink.description">Aktiviere Links zur Buchungsseite bei freien Tagen im Kalender.</label>
			<label index="showDateNavigator.description">Zeige Datumswahl oberhalb der Kalender.</label>
			<label index="numCheckDaySteps.description">Setzt die Tagesschrittweite im Verfügbarkeitscheeck Formular. Um nur Wochenbuchungen zu erlauben, setzen Sie diesen Wert UND numCheckMinInterval auf 7.</label>
			<label index="numCheckMaxPersons.description">Zeigt maximal die angegebene Anzahl von Personen in der Auswahl. Selbst wenn die Gesamtkapazität höher ist. Wenn der Wert leer ist wird automatische die maximale Kapazität ermittelt.</label>
			<label index="EmailAddress.description">Überschreiben der Absender-Email-Adresse: Dies wird die systemweite Konfiguration überschreiben. Um Spam-Header zu vermeiden, wird empfohlen TYPO3 für den systemweiten Versand per SMTP zu konfigurieren. In diesem Fall lassen Sie dieses Feld leer!</label>
			<label index="EmailRealname.description">Überschreiben des Absender-Namens: Dies wird die systemweite Konfiguration überschreiben. Um Spam-Header zu vermeiden, wird empfohlen TYPO3 für den systemweiten Versand per SMTP zu konfigurieren. In diesem Fall lassen Sie dieses Feld leer!</label>
		</languageKey>


	</data>
</T3locallang>
